acosmin.com 2019-07-09

# Terms & Conditions - Acosmin

Please carefully read, review and be sure you understand our Terms and Conditions of Use prior to downloading or using any of the products from Acosmin. You should carefully read all of our terms and conditions as your purchase or use of any Acosmin Product(s), or services and use of this Website and any materials or Products available herein identifies that you agree to the following Terms of Use and that you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions accordingly.

#### License & Usage

All our WordPress themes are licensed under the [GNU general public license](http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl.html).

You are allowed to remove any copyright information and you may modify the themes in any way you wish (php, html, css, images).

#### Support Policy

Support is provided for any theme purchased from Acosmin for a year after the purchase date. You will be guaranteed access to our support forums, knowledge base and documentation sections. 

We do not provide support for:

  * our free themes (except bugs and free updates);
  * the use or issues arising from the use of 3rd party plugins;
  * troubleshooting issues occurring in versions of Internet Explorer older than version 9.
  * installation, customization, administration of WordPress itself.

We will answer all support questions within 24-48 hours or faster. We are located in Europe (GMT+2) and you can expect a reply from us between 8am-7pm.

#### Theme Updates

Each time a new version of WordPress is released, we check our themes for compatibility with the new version, and we update them if this is required. Also we update our themes any time we discover a bug or when a new feature has been added to the theme.

All updates and new versions are free of charge for existing customers while their license is active.

#### Warranty/Compatibility

Our products are guaranteed to function on a clean installation of WordPress or when activated without any changes.

We cannot guarantee the compatibility of our themes with all third party software and plugins. If a conflict does arise, we will do our best resolve the situation. Moreover, we cannot guarantee the themes will function correctly after modification to the code, or a failure to install the theme or WordPress properly.

#### Refund Policy

All sales are final. No refunds will be given for software that is delivered via digital download from our site. If there is a problem with one of the digital download products or if you experience any difficulty with its download, we will fix the problem. Every theme sold on ACOSMIN has a fully functional “live” demo running the latest stable version of WordPress which can be tested at will.

We will be happy to answer any pre-sale questions regarding our themes before your purchase to insure it will meet your needs.

#### Privacy Policy

###### Who we are

Our website address is: http://www.acosmin.com

###### What personal data we collect and why we collect it

When registering on our Site you may be asked to enter your name, member name, email address, mailing address or other details to help you with your experience.

When you browse our Site, we also automatically receive traffic data registered by the hosting servers, cookies that may share some personal data and your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address. We also use information offered by other external services of traffic analysis, such as Google Analytics.

###### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

###### Contact forms

We do not use the information submitted through our contact form for any marketing purposes.

###### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

###### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

###### How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

###### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

###### Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

###### Our contact information

You can contact us regarding any privacy concerns or information by using this [contact form](http://www.acosmin.com/contact/)

###### How we protect your data

Your personal information is stored on secured servers and networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

All financial transactions are processed through a payment gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

#### Price Changes

ACOSMIN reserves the right to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, prices of all products or renewals, at any time with or without notice.

#### Affiliates

Affiliates will be paid each month for valid referrals generated from 2 months prior. There is no minimum number of referrals you need to generate before you can get paid. You must have a verified PayPal account.

We do not pay affiliates for unsuccessful transactions. We do not support spamming or the use of fake promotions as an affiliate. Abuse of the Acosmin affiliate program will result in nonpayment and removal from the program. We maintain close vigilance on each transaction and track where all sales are coming from. We do not support dishonest sales tactics. Unacceptable tactics which will result in nonpayment and possible termination include, but are not limited to:

  * Advertising coupon codes – including temporary promotional codes, expired codes, inaccurate discounts, or inaccurate payment details of any kind. Any coupon promotions are created for the benefit of our customers, not our affiliates.
  * Misrepresenting or inaccurately describing Acosmin services, products, brand, or trademark.
  * Misleading referred users in a manner which implies the inclusion of any product, service, or experience beyond that expressly depicted on acosmin.com.
  * Affiliates that sign up for the program and refer themselves for a discount on our products.
  * Fraudulent form leads.

If we have any reason to suspect fraud the affiliate will not be paid and the account will be terminated.
